<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- #BeginSnippet name="faq.xml" wysiwyg="no" -->
<FrequentlyAskedQuestions>
	<faq>
		<question>What is the Prayer Belts mission statement?</question>
		<answer>Our Mission is to Spread the Word, Strengthen the Commitment among the Faithful, Attract the Attention of the Un-Churched, Re-Engage the Curiosity of the De-Churched and Create Excitement with a Fun, Fashionable New Way to Pray.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What goal is Prayer Belts attempting to accomplish?</question>
		<answer>Our goal is to equip parents, young adults, teens, boys and girls - anyone of good faith - with a new weapon in the daily battle to profess faith in everyday life.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Who is behind Prayer Belts?</question>
		<answer>Prayer Belts were created by people deeply troubled over the systematic removal of prayer from public life for people who share the common desire to express their faith in public.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What are Prayer Belts?</question>
		<answer>Prayer Belts turns a common fashion accessory into a personal banner for displaying faith in places where such displays are often discouraged or prohibited by embroidering a faith-affirming message onto a stylish, color-fast web-style belt.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Which faith-affirming messages are available on Prayer Belts?</question>
		<answer>We are introducing Prayer Belts with two (2) faith-affirming messages:
			{ul}
				{li}In JESUS Name We Pray{/li}
				{li}JESUS Is My LORD and Savior{/li}
			{/ul}
		</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What is the Omega-style symbol on the front of each Prayer Belt?</question>
		<answer>The logo symbol on the front of each Prayer Belt is a combination of the "p" from prayer and the "b" from belt but it also resembles the Omega symbol, reminding people of Revelations 1:8 "I am the Alpha and the Omega", says the Lord God, "who is, and who was, and who is to come, the Almighty." and Revelations 22:13 "I am the Alpha and the Omega, the First and the Last, the Beginning and the End."</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What colors do Prayer Belts come in?</question>
		<answer>We are introducing Prayer Belts in black with the faith-affirming messages embroidered in white.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What are Prayer Belts made of?</question>
		<answer>Prayer Belts are made of 100% color-fast polyester.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>What sizes are available?</question>
		<answer>Each Prayer Belt is \"One Size\" 48\" long and 1 1/2\" wide.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>How much do Prayer Belts cost?</question>
		<answer>The special \"Introductory Price\" for each Prayer Belt is $19.95 plus Shipping &amp; Handling for all orders received by December 31, 2011.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>How much is Shipping and Handling?</question>
		<answer>Shipping and Handling for orders containing between 1 and 4 Prayer Belts is only $5.95, meaning there is no additional S&amp;H for customers ordering 2, 3 or 4 Prayer Belts.  Customers ordering more than 4 Prayer Belts will pay an additional $5.95 S&amp;H for every additional quantity up to 4 Prayer Belts per package.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Why are customers encouraged to order two (2) Prayer Belts at-a-time?</question>
		<answer>Customers who order 2 Prayer Belts at-a-time become even better equipped to support our stated mission to Spread the Word because they will have one belt to wear as a personal banner of faith and one belt to share with a relative, a friend, an acquaintance or a complete stranger looking to find their way.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>How do I pay for my Prayer Belt order?</question>
		<answer>All orders are made through the company's website, {a href='http://www.prayerbelts.com'}www.prayerbelts.com{/a} and are paid for by Credit Card (VISA, MasterCard, and American Express) or Debit Card.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Why is there no telephone number on the website?</question>
		<answer>There is no telephone number on the website because we believe it is more convenient for customers and visitors to communicate through the \"Contact Us\" section in the website.  We have done our best to anticipate every question our customers may have by providing answers in the FAQ section.  If you have a question that isn't answered in the FAQ section, then simply click on the \"Contact Us\" tab and send us an e-mail message.  We try to respond to e-mails within 48 hours.  If you do not receive timely reply, it means that we have not received your email or our reply has been filtered out by your spam filters. If this happens, please check your spam/bulk/junk mail folders or email us from a different email account.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>When can I expect delivery of my Prayer Belts?</question>
		<answer>Our goal is to fill each order within 24-hours and have it delivered within 7 days.</answer>
	</faq>
</FrequentlyAskedQuestions>
<!-- #EndSnippet -->
