<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- #BeginSnippet name="testimonials.xml" wysiwyg="no" -->
<testimonials>
	<testimonial>
		<text>My Prayer Belt looks great!  Lots of positive reaction when friends see me wearing it.  Doing what I can to Spread The Word.</text>
		<author>Jace C.</author>
		<city>McKinney</city>
		<state>Texas</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>I bought a Prayer Belt for my 10th Grade son and he wears it to school every day, bringing his faith into the classroom.  What a wonderful way to share our faith.</text>
		<author>Thomas P.</author>
		<city>McKinney</city>
		<state>Texas</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>I wanted to say "Thank You" for my Prayer Belts and the way they let me share my faith.  The quality of the belts is top-notch, with their clean embroidery and solid craftsmanship.  I have one of each and plan to order more as gifts so I can help Spread The Word.</text>
		<author>Katherine N.</author>
		<city>Brookfield</city>
		<state>Wisconsin</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>I love it when people ask me about my Prayer Belt because it let's me talk with them about the power of Jesus Christ in your life.</text>
		<author>Ron R.</author>
		<city>Ft. Mill</city>
		<state>South Carolina</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>America was built on a principle of religious freedom.  I bought a Prayer Belts because my religion is important to me and I want to let others know it's OK to show your faith in public.  The reaction from my friends and co-workers has been overwhelming.  Who'd have thought a belt with "In JESUS Name We Pray" on it would make such an impact?</text>
		<author>Robert W.</author>
		<city>Charlotte</city>
		<state>North Carolina</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>Kudos to Prayer Belts and y'alls staff for the speedy delivery of my Prayer Belts, the greatest new way to show off my love for Jesus.  The way it attracts others to ask me about my faith is amazing!  Who'd have thunk it?</text>
		<author>George W.</author>
		<city>Baton Rouge</city>
		<state>Louisiana</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>I love the power of "JESUS Is My LORD and Savior" and now I have such a convenient and useful way to express it to others.  Thank you, Jesus and thank you Prayer Belts!</text>
		<author>Austin G.</author>
		<city>Columbia</city>
		<state>South Carolina</state>
	</testimonial>
	<testimonial>
		<text>I guess they can't make my son remove THIS public display of faith because, as loose as he wears his jeans, they might have a bigger problem on their hands!  Seriously, thank you Prayer Belts for giving me and my son a way to bring our faith in Jesus into his public school.</text>
		<author>Rodney B.</author>
		<city>Corpus Christi</city>
		<state>Texas</state>
	</testimonial>
</testimonials>
<!-- #EndSnippet -->
